[theme music playing]
I heard your son Diego
tried to stop the project.
I'm sorry to say,
but if you can't control your son,
how can you control
the people of Ardiente?
I can't help but think
that if Grandpa were here,
we wouldn't be having these problems.
[Emilia] I'm the one here.
And I'm more than capable
of solving these problems.
-Wait!
-Miss Aguas! Miss Aguas!
[woman] Mr. Mayor, make them stop!
There's an innocent child here!
[clamoring]
[Arnaldo] Why can't you all understand?
This is for everyone!
-For the town!
-[Diego] Lies!
[Diego] It hasn't been 30 days
since you gave us the notice!
You don't have a court order
because we all know
this didn't go through due process.
The farmers will file an appeal!
[Ivy] Emilia, is this
what you really want?
[Emilia] We're Ardientes.
We get what we want.
[Ivy] Jepoy, I can't leave.
I'm with Emilia.
I know she's getting suspicious of me.
[Emilia] Ivy?
Who were you talking to?
Are you following me, Emilia?
[Diego] You have no right to hurt them!
I know you're just following orders,
but that's no reason
to act like criminals!
What we need
is the ownership of that land!
If you don't hand it back,
I will bring this issue
to your political enemies myself!
That way, no Ardiente will win
in the next election!
[townsfolk] That's right!
-[man] Nimfa, are you okay?
-[Loring] Nimfa?
Mr. Ramon got into an accident.
[goon] We're screwed, Governor.
Mr. Fernan's daughter saw me.
[Emilia] What?
But it's good that happened.
They'll realize they shouldn't be
going against the Ardientes.
Have you heard the news?
Someone from the co-op died.
Yes, it was Mr. Ramon.
Mr. Fernan's right-hand man,
leader of the co-op.
Another one bites the dust.
Life is really fleeting.
That's why
you have to celebrate your successes,
your little victories.
Otherwise, life is just
going to pass you by.
How sad.
Is that all you can say, Emilia?
Just the other day, Ramon
went here to plead with you.
[tense music]
Raul, are you insinuating I have
something to do with his death?
Not really.
But with all the people you had killed,
you might as well be the Grim Reaper.
Or maybe you're his proxy.
Just think about it.
You had your own son beaten up.
And what about Orallo?
I'm sure you had something
to do with his death
to cover up your gambling operations.
And now, you had a farmer killed?
I only did what I had to do
to save our family.
Because if I didn't, we would've
all gone down in flames!
[utensils clatter]
You always make decisions
without thinking of the consequences.
It's no wonder Grandpa
still can't trust you.
[tense music intensifies]
[Emilia] What's your point?
You think you're better than me
just because your grandfather
trusts you more?
You don't know how hard it is
to take his place.
I bear the pain
of making decisions for this family!
So don't you tell me that you know better
because, frankly, you won't
be able to handle it.
[unsettling music playing]
[sighs]
[squeals in frustration, heavy breathing]
[groans in frustration, heavy breathing]
[line ringing]
Vic, how's Grandpa? Is he conscious yet?
Not yet, Mayor.
Where's his doctor? I want to talk to him.
[Vic] All right, sir. Hold on.
Doc, Mayor Ardiente-Torillo
is on the line.
[York] Hello?
Doc, this is Mayor Ardiente-Torillo.
How's the congressman?
After his triple bypass operation,
we're closely monitoring
his body's reaction to the surgery.
When will he be discharged?
When can he come back?
It will take quite some time
for him to heal completely.
After which, we'll enroll him
in a comprehensive
cardiac rehabilitation program.
So, he will need some time.
Can I talk to him?
I'm sorry. He's still asleep.
But don't worry, we're taking
good care of him.
Okay, thank you.
[unsettling music playing]
[Diego] Mom!
Mom!
-Mom!
-And what's with that noise?
Mom!
Oh, you're here.
You didn't even bother to check on us.
-Should I still worry about you?
-That's not why I'm here!
And then, what?
Did you have Mr. Ramon killed?
[tense music intensifies]
Did you have him killed?
-What?
-Mr. Ramon.
The man who threatened to side
with our political enemies.
Did you have him killed?
Why are those farmers' future
more important to you
than the future of this town?
Mom, you don't have the right to decide
whether someone's life
is important or not.
You're just a governor, not a god!
[Arnaldo] Diego, that's enough.
Did you know about this?
It doesn't matter.
People die every day.
That's how life is.
You just have to deal with it.
[exhales]
You always tell me…
that I don't act like an Ardiente.
[melodramatic music playing]
[sniffles] I wish it was true.
I wish I wasn't born an Ardiente!
[melodramatic music playing]
I wish you weren't born
an Ardiente either.
If you're sick and tired of this family,
then, by all means, leave!
Do you understand?
I swear I won't come back here
until I prove you had a hand
in Mr. Ramon's death
and the other killings in this town!
[somber music playing]
[gun cocking]
[Emilia] You know, Ivy?
After all the stress
that I've gone through,
this is what I need.
[gunshot rings out]
[unsettling music playing]
[gun cocking]
[gunshot rings out]
Good job, there! Almost bull's-eye.
Yeah, almost. But it's not enough.
You should hit the heart, at the center,
where your enemies'
greatest desires and fears lie.
That's where you should aim at.
Well, Ivy, speaking
of enemies, take a look at this.
Look.
Read this article.
It seems like you're taking
Diego and the co-op's side.
Aren't they our enemies?
It's strange, Ivy, isn't it?
The very person
who will benefit from this project
is the same person delaying it.
You know, I just find it so weird.
Can you please enlighten me?
[tense music playing]
[chuckling]
Did you fall for that too, Emilia?
I must be a really good actress.
Emilia.
I'm a strategist.
First, I agreed to hold a dialogue.
Second, at the dispersal,
I showed everyone
how much I care for them.
Now, I know that they trust me.
I also know that they see me
as a true friend.
And before they know it…
Boom!
I already got what I want.
Really?
As for me…
I have two styles.
The first is the long route.
It's for the farmers
who I can get rid of like ants.
[gunshot rings out]
What's the second route?
Same as yours, Ivy.
But only deadlier.
That's why we're really
good friends, Emilia.
[gunshot rings out]
[gasps]
Bull's-eye?
So, I have to leave.
I still need to take care
of some business matters.
Okay, Ivy, thank you.
I'm happy that we're still
friends and allies.
Of course.
We're still allies, Emilia.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Good.
Just make sure you took care
of things smoothly.
Good job.
Ivy.
-Are you okay?
-My staff called.
One of my constituents just died.
It's so unfortunate, Ivy.
It was Mr. Ramon from the co-op.
[sighs] I forgot his last name.
You know what?
I have a feeling this happened
because he crossed someone.
I mean, it's so easy
to offend people these days.
You should always be careful.
Or else, you'll be one cold statistic.
Oh, um, Ivy, can you do me
a favor, please?
Can you send my condolences
to Mr. Ramon's family?
Can you also go to the wake on my behalf?
After all, you're my consultant.
[unsettling music playing]
I'll do it, Emilia.
But can I ask a favor too?
I hope we can put off the EPZ for now.
They just lost a member.
Things may just get worse.
Sure! We really should
put the project on hold for now.
Yeah.
I have to go.
All right. Bye, Ivy.
Are you really going to
the co-op like Emilia asked?
Why would I obey Emilia?
I just want to go to the co-op.
She wants you to take
the brunt of their anger.
It was one of their members, remember?
Ivy, it's too dangerous.
I don't want anything bad
to happen to you.
I can handle it, Jepoy.
I'm coming with you.
Jepoy!
Can you please stop?
Your job is to support my plans,
not to mess with my decisions.
[sighs]
Sorry.
Please try to understand.
Jepoy, I'm going to the co-op
not because Emilia asked me to.
I'm going there to pay my respects
because we both know
what Emilia did was wrong.
You know me.
I don't want to see anyone
being oppressed,
especially in the hands of the Ardientes.
I'm sorry too.
I was just worried about your safety.
I know.
What if Emilia doubts you?
Like I said, I know what I'm doing.
All right. I'll keep you posted.
NEW ARDIENTE
[Ivy] We've succeeded for now.
The Ardientes won't
take your land just yet.
I promise I will never forget
what happened to that farmer.
It's one of the crimes
the Ardientes will pay for.
I will get justice for his death.
And for my parents' deaths too.
[Nimfa] Have some biscuits.
If the Governor indeed had Ramon killed,
I think they want to send us a message.
They want us to stop going against them.
But what they're doing isn't right.
This is all your fault.
-What?
-Us?
This is Diego's fault.
You think you know everything.
In the first place,
we shouldn't have fought back.
We can't win against them, anyway.
Diego was just giving us false hope.
-Dolfo.
-That's not true.
Come on.
[phone ringing]
[car door clicks shut]
Hello, Joan?
Yes, okay.
Okay, sure. No problem.
All right, thanks.
[engine revving]
["Sa'Yo" by Silent Sanctuary playing]
Yes, madam?
Lara, would you know if Ivy
went to visit the co-op today?
Uh…
Yes, madam.
Miss Aguas scheduled a visit
to the co-op as your consultant.
Good.
-Miss Carlotta.
-Yes, Jepoy?
Is Ivy home yet?
Oh, I don't know.
She just said she's going to
drop by the co-op.
-The co-op?
-Yes.
She still went there.
-Okay, excuse me.
-Jepoy, wait.
Please don't worry about her too much.
Ivy can take care of herself.
We're here to love and support her.
That's our role in her life.
So, let's do it the best way we can.
Even if it hurts.
[phone ringing]
Hello, Mayor?
[Arnaldo] Report to me at my office.
Be there in 30 minutes.
Yes, sir.
[sighs]
I have to go.
All right. Take care.
Madam, won't you be going
with Miss Aguas to the co-op?
No.
Because that's her job as my consultant.
To tell you the truth,
I don't find her good at all.
She's been a failure lately.
Lucky for her, she's my friend.
I can see that you trust her
as your friend.
Well, let's just say
there is a close friend,
a best friend, or a casual friend.
And then, there's a frenemy.
But in times of crisis…
I'll save myself first.
Stop pointing fingers, Dolfo.
Diego did a lot of things for the co-op.
That's right.
If it weren't for him,
you wouldn't have a job.
If not Diego, then you're
the ones to be blamed.
-What?
-What have we done, Dolfo?
It's because you tried to befriend
that Miss Ivy Aguas!
You shouldn't have trusted that rich snob.
I bet she's the one who urged the Governor
to have my son killed!
-We don't know that, Dolfo.
-That's enough.
-[Dolfo] She had my son killed!
-[Loring] Hold on!
-If I see that Ivy Aguas…
-Mr. Dolfo, that's enough.
Mr. Dolfo, please sit down.
-Nimfa, get a cup of coffee…
-Diego!
-…so he'll come to his senses.
-Mr. Dolfo, you need to relax.
[Dolfo] Where is that woman?
Calm down, Mr. Dolfo.
Where have you been?
I've been waiting for you.
We're supposed to visit Natalie.
Madrigal.
What's wrong? You look distracted.
Mayor, I heard Miss Aguas
was going to visit the co-op.
Why would she go there?
She knows the farmers
have a rift with the Ardientes.
Natalie can wait.
Get the car. We're going to see Ivy.
Yes, Mayor.
[unsettling music playing]
Nimfa?
What are you doing here?
Nimfa, I'm here to pay my respects.
[Nimfa scoffs]
What for?
So you can play us for fools again?
-Nimfa, no--
-Oh, come on, Ma'am Ivy.
You came here with the Mayor last time.
You even helped us during the dispersal.
[scoffs]
But the truth is…
you're the one provoking
the Governor and the Mayor.
You know, Nimfa…
You can drop the act now.
You're just ruining our lives.
Nimfa, wait. Listen to me first.
I'm here to extend my sympathies.
I also want to tell everyone
that the project is on hold.
That's why I'm here.
[scoffs]
Wow!
Well, thank you for that.
You know what?
Ever since you came here,
there's been nothing but trouble for us.
-Nimfa.
-You know what you are?
You're a pest!
[squeals in pain]
Diego needs to know about this.
[Nimfa grunts]
Nimfa?
Are you okay? Come on.
-Let me help you.
-I don't need your help.
Nimfa.
I said I don't need your help!
-That's enough.
-My son…
Diego! Mr. Fernan!
-Nimfa's fighting with someone.
-What?
-[Fernan] Nimfa!
-Let's go.
Mario, look after Mr. Dolfo.
-Dolfo.
-[Diego] Nimfa!
Nimfa, I'm not your enemy.
Nimfa, I'm on your side.
Let me help you. Come on.
What's going on here?
Ivy?
Nimfa, what happened?
Uh…
Nimfa fell over, so I helped her up.
I'm really sorry. I just came here because
I want to offer my condolences
and to tell you that
the project is on hold.
Who made that decision?
Will it really happen this time?
We've heard that many times before.
After the dialogue, you told us
you'd look into our case.
But what did you do?
You ordered our dispersal.
-Mr. Fernan.
-[Loring] And now,
one of us died after protesting
against your project.
And now, you're telling us
the project's on hold?
Did someone have to die first
before you realized
what you're doing is wrong?
You know what?
Maybe it's best that you leave.
[unsettling music playing]
Mayor.
Madrigal.
How did you know that Ivy
went to the cooperative?
The Governor said so.
I heard her talking on the phone
and she mentioned that
Miss Aguas will go to the co-op.
Is that so?
Let's go.
Mr. Fernan, Nanny, Uncle.
-Let's hear her out--
-Diego.
It's okay.
I understand them.
[Dolfo] You!
-You monster!
-[screaming]
Mr. Dolfo!
[tense music playing]
-[Diego] Mr. Dolfo!
-[Nimfa] Mr. Dolfo!
-You're a monster!
-[Diego] Drop the machete!
That woman is a monster!
She's the one who put us in this mess!
They're stealing our land!
They're ruining our livelihood!
-[man] That's enough!
-Dolfo, stop it.
She's nothing but a greedy businesswoman!
-A greedy monster!
-Mr. Dolfo, that's enough!
We understand what you feel,
but you don't have to blame other people.
What's done is done.
-This isn't Ivy's fault!
-No!
We'll do everything to get justice
for Mr. Ramon's death.
It's her fault!
She must pay for this with her life!
-[man] That's enough, Dolfo.
-She needs to die!
-Let's go.
-That's enough.
-[man] Stop it, Dolfo.
-[Dolfo] It's her fault!
-[man] Let's go, Dolfo.
-[Dolfo] She's a thief!
[Dolfo screaming]
Ivy?
-[Ivy] I'll be going now.
-Ivy.
You're hurt.
-It's okay. I'll be fine.
-Ivy, wait!
We have to treat your wound.
Nanny.
Where's Raul?
Ma'am, he's at the porch,
talking to a woman.
A woman? Who?
[Raul chuckles]
[Raul] You look great.
You're still as beautiful as ever.
[Claire giggles]
Such a smooth talker, Raul.
I noticed you look younger.
-Come on.
-Tell me, are you in love?
Only with his beautiful wife and capable--
Aunt Claire?
Auntie, what are you doing here?
Really, Emilia?
After so many years
of not seeing each other,
that's how you greet me?
[scoffs] How about…
"I miss you, Auntie Claire?"
Of course, Auntie. Have a seat.
I missed you. My favorite
aunt and my mom's youngest sister.
I'm sorry I haven't visited in so long.
Even after your mom passed away.
You know how I never got along
with your boorish father.
And now that he's not around,
I figured now
is the best time to visit you.
Well, you just really
surprised me, Aunt Claire.
Why?
Do you have a weak heart like Julio?
Politics made you paranoid, my dear.
No, Auntie.
I just want to be sure that
the people who enter my house
are my allies and not my enemies.
Spoken like a true Ardiente.
[chuckles]
I'm sure my sister is so proud of you.
After all, you're now
the one sitting on the throne.
We should celebrate that, right?
Yes, Auntie. I missed you!
I missed you too.
-Welcome back.
-It's so nice to see you.
Wait here, Mayor.
[car door clicks shut]
Bro, hold on.
What's happening?
Mr. Dolfo got mad and grabbed a machete.
He tried to attack Miss Ivy.
Ivy?
Let's go. Move.
[Diego] Ivy, wait!
-Let's treat your wound.
-I can take care of myself.
You keep saying that,
but I won't believe you
because that's not what I see.
You don't know what you're saying
because you don't know me.
I just want to make sure you're okay.
What Mister Dolfo did was wrong.
I said I'm fine.
And, Diego, I understand.
I understand why they're blaming me.
I shouldn't have come here
because I know you all see me as an enemy
since you know I'm an ally
of the Ardientes.
That's why I understand why
the people here are mad at me
and why you are too.
Hold on. Don't generalize us.
I'm not Mr. Dolfo.
I don't look at you the way they do.
I stood up for you, remember?
Did I ask you to do that?
Do you think…
I'd ever let you get hurt?
["Sa'Yo" instrumental playing]
You're concerned?
Wait a minute.
Mr. Torillo, you're mad at me.
So, please, don't pretend
that you're concerned about me.
Could you just stop doubting me?
That's how I really feel!
Really now? That's how you feel?
Aren't you mad at me?
All you've ever done was despise me!
What was it you said?
That ever since I arrived
at Poblacion Ardiente,
I've brought nothing but trouble.
That I'm greedy for money,
like your family.
That I'm using your brother
and your mother for this project.
So don't tell me that you're
worried or concerned about me!
What?
Are you eating your words now?
["Sa'Yo" by Silent Sanctuary playing]
Let's go.
[tender music playing]
[heavy breathing]
[breathes heavily]
No, Ivy.
Don't.
-Driver, let's go.
-[car engine starts]
Ivy.
Ivy, wait!
Ivy!
Diego, where's Miss Ivy?
Has she left? Was she hurt?
Where's Mr. Dolfo?
Back there.
[deep breath]
So, Diego's trying to pull
a fast one on me.
Make sure you find the man
who tried to hurt Ivy.
[unsettling music playing]
-We understand how you feel,
-Mr. Dolfo.
-but you should take it easy.
-Mr. Dolfo, why did you do that?
I'm sorry, Diego.
My anger got the best of me.
I know we're all angry right now,
but that's not an excuse
to resort to violence.
Everyone,
I know it's hard to start again
after what happened,
but we have to believe that
if we work together,
we'll be able to bounce back.
-That's right!
-We need to stay united.
That's right. As long as
we help each other.
-We have to help each other.
-You're not alone, Dolfo.
Let's help each other.
[tense music playing]
[man] The cops are here.
Good evening. We're looking
for Rodolfo Makabisbis.
That's me.
We have a warrant for your arrest.
You're coming with us.
Hold on. What did he do?
He went berserk
and threatened Miss Aguas' life.
Wait. Maybe we can talk this out--
It's all right, Diego.
This is my fault.
Miss Aguas has every right
to have me arrested.
-[police] Take him in.
-You're coming with us.
-Take it easy.
-Gently, Officer.
-Let's go.
-Diego.
-Sir.
-Dolfo.
[indistinct chatter]
Mr. Dolfo, don't worry.
We'll help you get out of there.
Diego, where are you going?
Nanny, if Ivy's the one
who had Mr. Dolfo arrested,
she's the only one who can free him.
I'll be right back. I won't take too long.
Uncle, you take care of everything here.
-Take care, Diego.
-Everyone, I'll be back.
Ivy, you have to be
more careful next time.
Look what happened.
It could've been worse!
[sighs]
Nanny, I'm fine.
Anyway, Diego was there.
He stood up for me.
Well, it's a good thing he did.
Even though you don't get along,
he still came to your rescue.
Ivy.
Don't you think it's about time
you told Diego the truth?
He's already going against his family.
I believe he'll side with what's right
and help you seek justice.
[somber music playing]
It's not that easy.
It's way too complicated.
He actually kissed me earlier.
What?
He kissed you? Why?
I don't know. It's so hard to read him.
I mean, one day he's mad at me
and then, we're friends.
Later, he'll get mad again.
Earlier, he said
he was concerned about me,
that's why he wanted to help.
Then, I got so confused,
so I confronted him about
the harsh things he's ever told me.
Until it… happened.
He kissed me.
What?
[scoffs]
You know, Nanny.
Ms. Prianka taught me…
to always prepare for the unexpected.
[sighs]
But not for this.
Ivy!
-[doorbell rings]
-Ivy!
-Ivy, what should I do?
-Ivy! Ivy!
-I'll tell him you're asleep.
-Ivy!
-Ivy, well?
[door clicks open]
Yes?
What are you doing here?
-Well?
-About what happened earlier…
You meant the kiss?
[sighs]
Diego.
It's fine.
It's not a big deal.
But I shouldn't have done that.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
As I said earlier,
it was just a kiss.
It's nothing.
If that's why you're here,
you can leave now.
Ivy, wait.
I really came here for Mr. Dolfo.
I know what he did was wrong,
but please don't have him arrested.
Arrested? I didn't have him arrested.
But the cops came by to arrest him.
I had nothing to do with it.
If it wasn't you, who had him arrested?
Let's find out.
-Nanny Carlotta?
-[nanny] Yes, dear?
-Please get my bag.
-[nanny] Your bag? Coming right up.
Here you go.
Diego and I are going to the precinct.
-Okay, dear.
-I'll ride with you.
Let's go.
[unsettling music playing]
The Mayor had him arrested.
Of course, he did.
He really cares about
his constituents of this town.
Sir, I was the one who got hurt,
and I don't plan on pressing charges
against Mr. Dolfo,
so, please, release him now.
Okay, ma'am.
Since you won't press charges,
we can't keep him in here.
Release Rodolfo Makabisbis.
-Let him out.
-[officer] Rodolfo.
It's Mr. Dolfo. Sir, thank you very much.
-Diego.
-You're welcome, Ms. Aguas.
Thank you, Officer.
Thank you, Diego.
Thank you, Miss Ivy.
Please forgive me for what I did.
[sniffling]
It's all right, Mr. Dolfo.
I understand why you did that.
I know how it feels.
[melancholic music playing]
I know the pain…
of losing a loved one.
I understand how you feel.
You're such a good person, Miss Ivy.
Thank you so much, ma'am.
Thank you, Diego.
[melancholic music playing]
Ivy, thanks again for helping
Mr. Dolfo get out of jail.
It's nothing.
What you said earlier…
about knowing how it feels
to lose a loved one…
I don't want to talk about it, Diego.
I know you're still mad at me.
I'm sorry. I know what I did was wrong.
But I hope you'll forgive me.
Diego.
You've already apologized so many times.
Yes, I forgive you.
So, please, let's not talk
about this anymore.
Okay.
Thank you.
Just forget about what happened.
[melancholic music playing]
[engine starts]
I really hate it when someone
tries to take what's mine.
[unsettling music playing]
And I hate being betrayed.
People who go behind my back.
I need to talk to you.
About what?
About how you used Miss Aguas
to get Dolfo out of prison?
Or maybe, about what her lips taste like?
I saw you two.
Do you think I liked what you did?
I don't need your permission
to kiss any woman I want.
Well, you can kiss anyone you want…
except Miss Aguas
because she's mine.
[scoffs]
Wow, Arnaldo.
You still haven't changed.
You're like a kid.
You still think you own whoever you like.
Hmm.
[tense music playing]
So, who's the scared kid now?
Go ahead.
Shoot me!
Pull the trigger!
[rifle cocks]
[tense music intensifies]
Mayor.
[tense music fades]
Arnaldo, Diego.
Arnaldo, cut that out.
What's wrong with you two?
[Arnaldo sighs]
My brother's so brave!
But let me just remind you
that Ivy is mine.
And if I see you
hovering around her again…
[clicks tongue]
[unsettling music playing]
That's Diego, Auntie,
picking a fight with Arnaldo again.
You'd think after he leaves this house,
he'd disappear for good.
[chuckles] But I don't
want to think about him.
It sounds like Diego's a pain in the neck.
His very existence is a pain.
I really admire the sacrifices
you've made, Emilia.
You really love this family,
especially Raul.
I'm so glad you see that.
Meanwhile, my father…
and other people,
they all think I'm a fool.
But I really don't care what they think.
I love Raul.
I love my family.
I love being an Ardiente.
I have to hold this together,
no matter what happens.
[unsettling music playing]
And how is your father doing?
I don't know. I don't want to know.
And why not?
Aren't you excited for him
to return alive and limping?
Not now.
I'm just getting started.
You're only just starting to fail, Emilia.
I'm updated on everything
that's happening here.
And all I can say is
you still have a long way to go
to be at par with your father.
I can surpass all he's done.
I just need to be more careful.
I can't afford to make any more mistakes.
I'm here to help you.
That's why I'm back.
For your success, dear.
I'm just here to get my other things.
[door clicks shut]
I guess you're really going
to leave this house, huh?
Son.
Diego.
Whatever happened between you and Arnaldo,
I hope you can let it go.
Dad.
I'm so sick and tired
of understanding him.
-She's just a woman, son.
-This isn't just about Ivy.
This is about everything he's done to me.
Son, you know your brother.
You know what he can do.
-I'm not scared of him.
-Well, I'm scared for you.
So, keep out of his way
as much as you can.
What for, Dad? So he can bother Ivy again?
He already has Natalie.
Why does he even need Ivy?
Why? Do you like Ivy?
[tender music playing]
[sighs] I can't explain
how I feel about her.
But it feels like I've known her
for a long time.
I want to get to know her more.
I want to protect her from Arnaldo.
[tender music intensifies]
Butchoy has a love letter for you.
Butchoy is so cute.
I guess I've got more competition now.
Are we celebrating something?
It's final. I'm running for Senate.
[Pablo] I have
a different candidate in mind.
A different candidate?
I like the sound of that.
Miss Aguas, I was born to lead.
And this is my chance.
I'd rather support Emilia than you.
What can I do to change your mind?
The farmers' land.
Are you doing this
for the farmers or for Diego?
[Ivy] It's not my fault if your brother
moves faster than you.
[theme music playing]